



EDUCATION

PERSONAL

Name Samuel Svensson Birthday July 10, 1995 Nationality Swedish

Languages Swedish, English, (Spanish)

ABOUT ME

I'm a 23 year old Master of Science student that has a passion for creative programming and smart solutions. I've mostly been doing web-development in Javascript but I am always open for opportunities to learn something new. One of my greatest ambitions is to work with 3D-computer graphics and image processing combined with challenging programming assignments!

CONTACT

Mobile +46 725444332

Email samuel.svensson.95@gmail.com

Address Skomakaregatan 9

602 32 Norrköping

LINKS

Portfolio: samuelllsvensson.github.io

Linköping university Norrköping, SE 2016-Present - Master of science in Media technology

Programming, computer graphics, visualization and design.

Selected courses:	Course code:
Programming (C++)	TND012
Electronic publishing	TNMK30
Object-oriented programmering	TNA003
Computer Graphics	TNM046
3D-Computer Graphics	TNM061
Programming in C++ (Continuation course)	TNG032
Communication and user interfaces	TNM040
Modelling and simulation	TNG022
Signals and systems	TNG015
Image processing and analysis	TNM087

Västerhöjdsgymnasiet (high school) Skövde, SE - Teknikprogrammet 2011-2014 Information and media technology

EXPERIENCE

Agricam AB Linköping, SE 2019/06 - 2019/08 - Software Intern I built a RESTful API and ported the company's internal status system from a Windows application (C#) to the web using React + Redux

Cygni Norrköping, SE - Student brand manager 2018-Present I represent Cygni at campus and coordinate events for the students

Linköping university

Norrköping, SE - Teaching assistant 2017/09-2018/01 Assisted younger students in a web development course.

Summer jobs: Engine & AC assembler, warehouseman 2015-2017

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES / SOFTWARE

JAVASCRIPT/REACT/JQUERY, HTML5, CSS3/BOOTSTRAP, C++, GIT, NPM. MATLAB, ADOBE PHONEGAP, ADOBE-SUITE & OFFICE 365. SOME JAVA, PHP AND C# EXPERIENCE.